Let's talk about the
fwd set for tomorrow.
This product has three variants: income
protector, estate protector, and
short-term cover. In short-term cover, some are
called regular and some are called
digital. So what is set for tomorrow? This
is a term insurance plan that is
renewable every 5 years and 10 years. It
is convertible to permanent plans if
in the future you see that
permanent plans are more beneficial.
You can convert it. The minimum
coverage for regular is at least 1
million provided 21,000. At least
his annual premium for digital is
Php1 million but up to a
maximum of not more than 5 million
provided his premium is at least
12,000 per year. What age can
take it? For regular, it is at least 18 to
70 years old. For digital, it is 25 to 55 years
old. Let's talk about
its coverages. Number one life insurance.
So we already know that if the
insured has a debt, how much life
insurance coverage will the
beneficiary receive as stated in the policy
contract?  number two terminal illness
benefit
will be added if the insured has a terminal illness,
which means that the term has been given
within 12 months, the fund will be advanced
and the policy will be terminated number three
overseas benefit if the death
occurs abroad, an additional
20% of his life insurance will be
given to the beneficiary or php500,000
whichever is lower next benefit is
the funeral benefit when the
insured dies, fwd will advance 10% of the
insured's coverage within 48 hours next
benefit is the spouse Extension
benefit automatic coverage for your
spouse when there is a death in the same
identity both the insured and the spouse
provided they have a minor child at
least one minor means below 18 years old
so therefore the insurance
proceeds will be doubled let's talk about what are
the advantages that we have seen in
this product number one
we have seen this is one of the cheapest the
cheapest term insurance
we have seen it only reaches less than
php3 per
his premium at age 18 years old
using a digital product next I
locked in his premiums for at least
5 years or 10 years unlike other term
insurance he is renewable every year so
therefore his premium is
changing It will be increased every year here
he is locked for 5 years there is no
change unless after 5 years or
10 years next is the guaranteed
renewability after 5 years of
your payment or 10 years of your payment you want to
renew him there is no application
process that will happen he is automatic
you can renew him next the
advantage we saw is the terminal illness
benefit in other insurance plans
the insured must actually die
before we can give the proceeds
while here fwd considered that As if
the person who was given tanning is already living that is why
the proceeds are given immediately
it is advised [Music] But there is still a chance that it will happen
I see it as an advantage because What
if you go to another country
and something unexpected happens an
additional coverage on top of the
basic life insurance coverage
our beneficiary will receive which is
not in  other terms insurance
next advantage is the spouse
Extension benefit Although same with
overseas benefits the spouse Extension
benefit is very uncommon that it happens that
a couple will have an untimely
death in the same accident rarely but it does
happen no the fact that there is
this feature in fwd set for
tomorrow I consider it an advantage next
is the funeral benefit this is one of the
features that we have appreciated once because if
there is a death in our loved
ones aside from the emotional damage no
that we or the bereaved family are going through
during those times What is the
reality that you will face the
expenses from hospital bills to
funeral and burial expenses those are the
realities that you will face in
those moments you need to need
immediate funds So I saw an
advantage and I appreciated it because
imagine that the 10% of the coverage in insured will be
added to the expenses on those bills that
we mentioned next advantage is
easy to avail because you can
avail it via online there is no financial
advisor or insurance advisor to go through
if that is what you want  You can
avail it but please take note that you can only avail up to
4 million
999,999
maximum
life insurance coverage through digital
when we reach 5 million
coverage we also need
access to a financial advisor of fwd
next advantage of this product there is no
limit to the coverage for as long as that is what
you need and
your budget can afford next advantage according
to the manager we spoke to at fwd the
filing of claims is via online next
advantage I saw is that it has the option
of modal premium meaning
we can pay even quarterly there are
other term insurance per anum Or
every year the payment is so it is easier
if it is every 3 months next
advantage we saw is that the premium
payment method we can pay
online online banking credit card
we can debit or
autocharge let's talk about the
disadvantages we saw number
one minimum of 1 million is life
insurance cov coverage for you to avail
this product not all
bread winners need 1 million
life insurance coverage  so that means
there are families who cannot avail
of this product, it is not suitable for
families like them, next is
its minimum premium which is 12,000 per
anum Not all bread winners
can afford to pay 12,000 per year or
around 3,000 per quarter or ah the
average is 1,000 per month So there are
families or Bread winners who are not that
The budget that is all-Cate for
their insurance needs next
disadvantage that I saw here in the
shortterm cover since its paying period
can be 5 years and 10 years
It does not have a waiver of premium in case of
disability in other variants I believe
there is a waiver of premium that can be attached
but in the shortterm cover there is none
so for whom can I recommend this
number one for people with
dependents how can we determine if
the people around us are
dependent of course
our family So how can we
determine that our family is dependent let's
ask ourselves
if we are lost  We are the Lord who has taken us and
they will suffer
severe financial loss or financial
damage. If yes, then we can consider
them dependents, so therefore we have
dependents, so I recommend it
to those who have dependents. Next, for those
who want to add coverage,
maybe your dependents have increased,
your
financial obligations have increased, then you can
consider increasing your coverage.
So I can recommend this to you for those who
have paid MOR gauges
like housing loans, car loans, and
other types of loans. We can
use it as our MOR gage Redemption
insurance, so that if something
unexpected happens to us,
our family will not be charged.
I can also recommend it to those who just
want a plain and simple
life insurance plan that doesn't have any
other features or
they say, "ok-ok." Next, I can also recommend
it to those who at least have a
budget of 12,000 a year or around 1,000
a month. So if you have that kind of
budget, Yes, you can.  this product is
SAO things to consider before getting a
life insurance number one do you
really need life insurance because
if you don't then
the premiums are just a waste
two what type of plan and how much
coverage do you really need number
three do you really have the budget for it
If you think this is the product
you are looking for this is the fit and perfect SAO
just click on the link you see
somewhere in the description or caption
and you can process your
application via online and if you think
4,999 n99
coverage is not enough you need at least 5 million please
message us
so that we do
n't have to suffer or
hurt our pockets unnecessarily So thank you, I
hope you learned something from
our product review God bless
and hope to see you soon